export const quizData = [
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Basics",
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
    explanation: "HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages.",
  },
  {
    title: "HTML5 Structure",
    question:
      "Which tag is used to define the main content of an HTML document?",
    answer: "<main>",
    explanation: "The <main> tag specifies the main content of a document.",
  },
  // Add more questions here...
];
